Please subscribe to my channel!
I'll do my best!
Look at my yellow bangs.
Oh my god! Look at Aki-chan!
Gotta be kidding me, right?
Everyone has gone crazy hearing their
unit name!!
We must make an entrance!
We are preventing an opening!
They will begin the opening performance
phrased with...
There are six of us who are trying new
things in this show
We're going to raise the excitement
level in the world!
We're ready!
3, 2, 1...
No!
Oh, I'm in.
I'm in.
OK, Kamiyana, go ahead.
Thank you for coming to the beginning
of the 2020-2021 Tokimeki Parade of the
Tokimeki Advertising Club's Tokimeki
Summer Spring Stage.
I'm Hito-chan, also known as Chou
Tokimeki Red, and I'm Hitoka Sakai.
I'm Hiyorin, also known as Chou
Tokimeki Green, and I'm Hiyori
Yoshikawa.
Thank you for having us!
Before we start the show, we would like
to ask you to pay attention to the
following.
The audience in the front row of the
first floor, the audience in the family
area,
The audience in the family area,
The audience in the family area, cannot
watch the show from the top.
Please enjoy the show while you are
seated.
We will be starting soon.
I'm so excited!
The audience in the back row,
Let's ask them if they are excited.
Are you excited?
Yeah!
They are excited like this.
Are you excited?
Yeah!
Thank you!
See you later!
It's a bit too much.
Tanomi! Chiria! Hitoka! Haruka! Aki!
Hiwari!
Super Exciting Advertising Club!
Let's go!
Thank you for watching!
Please subscribe to my channel!
We always meet in front of Shibuya
Tsutaya
You are a little faster than me
I'm waiting with earphones
If you come closer from behind and tap
my back
Ireated by someone and you laughed
And I clung to the gentle you
A doun on an older brother
This is a charming point.
Maybe you can lose your form a bit
while being kept under the wind.
When I Icelande her under, I always
fly.
The urge to go further
You've done yourself in good shape over
there.
No matter how sweaty you sweat,
That's cute♥
TOLookEngine.com
I'm going to go to the encore stage.
Buy ice cream
You laugh and say sorry
I'm a kind bird
Hey, I want you to be cute forever
I want to be your type
I'm worried about you
Buy ice cream
Thank you!
Please come again!
Bye!
Thank you!
No problem.
Thank you very much.
I want to record it forrica D numero
ust me.
Isn't it a Dume-she?
The staff members who came to see the
mansion
Today's sunrise
There is another morning
Let's rest well.
Thank you.
We'll do our best.
Let's go.
We're done. Thank you for your hard
work.
This is crazy.
Really.
At first,
I thought we could do 50 free live
shows.
But we couldn't.
We started from the beginning.
From there,
we did live shows
in the hall
and in the live house.
But we couldn't fill the space.
We really
wanted to go to the auditorium.
We wanted to go to the auditorium.
But we didn't know if we could.
We were a little overwhelmed.
But we did today's live show.
We thought we could go to the arena.
We thought we could come here
together.
We were so happy.
We were grateful
to everyone.
We had a lot of emotions
like we finally did it.
We were so happy.
I'm still a newbie, so I'll do my best
not to cry tomorrow.
I'm going to eat this.
I haven't seen this yet.
You haven't seen it?
I'll give it to you next time.
I'll eat it all.
Where are you going?
I'm not going anywhere.
I'll do my best tomorrow.
I'll do my best.
I'll show you my cool side.
It was fun.
I've talked a lot, so I'm going to go
eat crepes.
I'm going to go to the refrigerator.
I'll go to the refrigerator.
Please subscribe to this channel.
A scene of an epic fight of magical
powers.
Five members formed for the third day
of RSS.
hosting RSS
And the first day was over!!
We did it!
It was easier than I thought.
I don't know if it's because I'm on a
truck.
It was so quick.
It was easier than I thought because I
could see Senemui-san up close.
Our eyes met.
I'm so happy.
How was it, everyone?
How was it, Senki-kun?
Please tell us that you love us every
day.
Please tell us.
I went to MC2.
I danced with Chiria and Aki-chan.
It was my first time.
I'll do my best.
You were so cute when you said, hurry
up.
You were so serious.
It was a different atmosphere because
it was a truck.
The choreography is more fun.
Please look forward to it.
I'm not waiting for you.
Everyone said,
there's a crepe!
It's been a while since we had one.
We haven't had one yet.
We haven't.
We'll eat it!
We'll do our best to get better
tomorrow!
It's fun, so let's do it quickly.
We'll do our best!
Bye-bye!
Next!
It was our first time at Arena Armour.
So,
it wasn't just our Arena.
It wasn't just our Arena.
So,
it was like,
it was our own Arena.
I know.
That feeling.
Some people
said that
we've performed at
various festivals
and had a lot of audience.
But,
we said that
we wanted to perform at the Arena.
But, we didn't know
if we could perform there
until we got the tickets.
So,
I was happy.
There were so many people.
360 degrees.
We were
riding a tricycle
at a close distance.
It was closer than we thought.
It was right in front of us.
We could see the inside of the arena.
We could see
the faces of our fans.
So, I was happy.
It was fun.
It's fun to perform at the Arena.
We'll be able to perform at the Arena
someday.
Let's make memories at the Arena!
We will.
Thank you for today.
We'll do our best!
Ready?
Rehearsal finished
Thank you!
Hiyori-san, I want you to reflect on
yourself
What?
Your first impression of Kage Nari?
Was it okay?
It was great
Really? I think I was wrong
I did it before on YouTube
Thank you for watching!
Well, that's...
It was good
It was good if it was fun
It was a good opening
It was great from the beginning
It was fun
It was fun to do it
Leave it there
How was it?
The stage
I was like this
It's been 3 years
And the first song, Sonic Adventure
I felt like I was going to fight
Live house
I know how to say
How did you feel?
Live house
It's not live house
It's like a hall
It's like an arena
We are in an arena
We are standing
How did you feel?
I know
When Sonic Adventure started
It's not like this song is coming
It's like a song that makes the
atmosphere
Let's go!
It's like that
Today's Sonic Adventure came so fast
What's this feeling?
It's really
And the truck
It was the first time
I didn't think there would be one
person
It's been a while since we did a live
I was happy to see everyone's
expressions
I was nervous at first
It was fun
To come this far
Free live
People were like this
Arena
I'm happy
It's crazy
It's not Sonic Adventure
It's not
Is there a double performance?
I'll do my best without losing my
temper
I feel like I got it today
Like this
I got it
I'll do my best tomorrow
Before going to bed
Let's take a rest
Let's rest
I'll do my best tomorrow
Bye
I'm sure someone is crying somewhere
I'll share my feelings with you
If you enjoyed today's Tokiwara
If you think today's video was cute and
interesting
Please subscribe and like!
We're waiting for your comments!
Bye-bye!
Please subscribe to my channel!
I can say it now, I won't hesitate to
shed tears
I remember the time we met
Even if it rains, I'll smile
Look, let's go anywhere
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I ring the bell of the rainbow
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye, goodbye, to me of yesterday
The city after the rain is sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day
I cry my tears
I wear a rainbow dress
Thank you for watching!